this is class number three ACI course
number three which is meditation applied
meditation
what's the applied mean yeah something
you can use in your real life
okay not for hippies to stay in jungle
okay okay so we had the six steps of
preparation one of them Suk Jong
included seven different ingredients and
tonight you get another six yay but
don't confuse it with the other six okay
these are not preparations for
meditation they are conditions that you
need for good meditation okay and these
are from Maitreya and who got them from
my trailer ah Sangha after he met the
dog okay and he brought back the lions
dance and he brought back the teaching
on the conditions for meditation
the Maitreya taught five famous books
this one is called Sutra alankara and we
haven't studied it much okay sutra means
the ancient teaching of the buddha
alankara means jewel jewelry okay
jewelry I like this word my teacher
Sanskrit teacher he liked it he Allah
Allah means to get ready for a party
Allah Allah means ready for a party
cara means you learned it to make so
jewelry is called alankara the thing you
need to get ready for the party it's the
name for jewelry okay in sanskrit
al-ankara it means get ready the stuff
you have to put on to get ready for the
party
it's called allen cutter the teaching on
the six conditions you need for good
meditator
come from a book called the jewel of the
citrus meaning the most precious thing
from the sutras is taught by the future
Buddha which is Maitreya
the book is called suture say Sutra
Allan Connor it just means I will give
you the cream of the sutras I will give
you the most delicious part from that I
will give you the your child of the
sutras okay and then later a Sangha used
it in his famous series of books called
the books on the levels like the levels
of Bodhisattvas the levels of listeners
it's a very complicated series of books
that he wrote ok yoga challenge
Yoga charter Bumi and then later a
teacher from India a guru from India
named Camila Sheila who wrote the great
commentary the diamond cutter which I'm
still working on ok I didn't stop it
will come out
[Music]
he also wrote three famous books called
Bhavana namaste Pomona crumber
Havana Rama stages of meditation and I
taught them during their common-law
Sheela series which was before the new
gorillaz series I taught them they're
not very long
Timmy ready now my teachers teacher who
is the Teacher of the dollar the current
dynamo which is - jongmin / - he was my
teachers rude teacher so your
great-grandfather is the teacher of this
dialogue Junior teacher who was they
think the greatest teacher of of those
times his teacher was pop uncle who
wrote the famous mum room so this is
your lineage you are poor mocha
t-jon can remember to goosy muku and
then you okay so you are in this
miniature okay you are in a very you
should be proud of your I'm direct
descendent of Camelot Sheila you know
cuz you are okay you really are so
common cheat I remember chain I don't
know if it's pictures here he had this
carving name
he had this carving he ordered this
carving made he and he designed it and
it includes all of the Bhavana chroma it
includes all of Camelot Sheila's
instructions for meditation
okay so DCI course these are level three
and a CI course three are based strongly
on this chart and I never taught the
whole thing to anybody and maybe once I
translated the whole thing but it's
amazing so if someday if you really have
time we can go deeper but tonight's
class about the six conditions for
meditation comes from Camilla Sheila
okay
this is teacher opportunity
extraordinary teacher unbelievable
teacher you can't imagine you can't
imagine I lived next door to him for six
months and I never went to see him
because I didn't want to bother him
everybody went to see him and I said no
I'm gonna be cool I don't want to bother
he asked people bother him all the time
then when I told my teacher he gave me a
massage on the head
so anyway we can study that chart
it's a beautiful chart it's an amazing
okay and we can go deeper okay
a lot of the three-year retreat ins here
used it right you guys used it very
heavily I think yeah for three years
they they used it they used to have
fights about what level their own
meditation level fights I'm on level 43
no you're not
yeah I'm nama 38 okay here we go six
okay these are sick conditions for
meditation they are different from six
preliminaries okay and definitely not
the same as the seven ingredients okay
number one and I'm gonna read the the
reading okay where's that yeah okay I
gave you I translated it from so Coppola
memo okay the reading is from the
momentum and he I gave you the the six
first condition the place should be a
good place for meditation the place
should be a good place for meditation we
called tune can Satan can tinkin means
it's a good meditation place Diamond
Mountain is one of the best in the world
I think so okay so on a small level in
your apartment make a special space that
you don't use for other things okay and
you know most of us we can't afford to
build another room or something so use
part of the living room or something but
make it a sacred space and don't use it
for other things okay and those this
first one
are you ready if you want to go deeper
it has five
okay no don't get confused okay we're
talking about six conditions for good
meditation and the first one which is it
should be a good place for meditation it
has five parts okay and I you don't have
to teach this when you teach it I didn't
put it on the homework okay now
everybody stop writing
maybe it's under humming maybe not okay
so let's go through it you should have a
source of food and clothing okay you
gotta have a job I'm sorry you should
have told us so I young dhaba is a
buddhist practice called get a job it's
a very famous practice there are five
parts of that but I'm not going to teach
you that okay but you should have an
honest income okay it's it's not a good
thing to say I'm a meditator and Brian
should pay for it
Brian should go work and geshe michael
should stay at Diamond Mountain
meditating this is not the way it should
be okay you should go out work I had
friends they told me yes like I just
want to go to Diamond Mountain meditate
I can't get a job then I got a list of
how many people in Arizona have a job
it's five million or something I said
look five million people around you
found a job you know you're a Buddhist
you're smart person okay if five million
stupid people can find a job then you
can package don't tell me you're
Buddhist you know you got all these four
steps talk okay all right same way
now some of these instructions are
relating to retreat okay some this
instruction especially means don't try
to do retreat in a strange place okay do
retreat in a place where people are
bringing you food so my retreat I had
1,000 days of retreat
I had three thousand meals that jing-mei
made for me and other kind people okay
we have a long history of she's giving
me food
but we fundraised for it before we
started we treat mostly so three
thousand meals you gotta have support
okay
it means you have to have support okay
if you're gonna do serious meditation
you should have a job it shouldn't be a
80 hour a week job because then you
don't have to visit so you have to
balance okay you have to balance maybe
you won't make as much money as you
could have made if you didn't meditate
or maybe you will make even more money
if you militate guidance so anyway the
first thing about the place especially
if a retreat it's a you need a place
like that okay where it's built for
retreat it's built for meditation it
exists for meditation and I really
really really really really really
really feel don't wait for caching
Michael to teach the gardener come come
to that mountain this is your place you
all donated to this place you know it's
your place also it's not owned by me I'm
also just visiting okay bring five
people bring ten people really you crazy
if you don't do it
have a party have a meditation party
from your country this is your place
okay
just as sinem or gal stay okay just ask
them we want to bring ten people from
Shanghai
okay cool do it it's places for you this
is your place okay this is not owned by
anybody it's your place okay so you're
crazy if you if you don't bring ten
people Vietnam you know get five in
Hanoi five and Ho Chi Minh's
maybe some young people twelve people
then come between Thai up mr. bean put
him on the airplane
it's your place okay it's your place
you're crazy
Singapore people get organized you know
don't wait for Jenny one she's too busy
as sanam talk to sinem say we wanted the
retreat can we have ten days can we have
the place for ten days and we have room
we have room for them we have time okay
just just I think you're crazy if you
don't come here on your own you don't
have to wait for me you can do more
meditation when I not teach you know I
mean when I'm here learn the stuff and
then come on your own and come for ten
days and take a vacation
take a darling vacation okay just do it
okay
this is your place okay we have the time
we are not booked up and it breaks my
heart the place is empty everyone needs
retreat and they just talk to cinema you
don't need Tim to organize the guards
you know Ricci
just make a plan talk to your friends
let's go okay let's go you could go back
to China and Vietnam Singh I own a place
in in Arizona
it's the largest retreat center in
America
this is 1,000 acres okay 1,000 acres
okay this is like miles and miles
on all these mountains okay I have a
private place retreat place in essence I
can get you in you know it's the largest
Indian eyes instantly I think it's the
largest in the United States it's
possibly the largest in the world
okay we own all those mountains okay and
just come you can brag about it and the
food oh my god they're Mapo tofu is
better than Chengdu and K small lies
okay if to bring people on the chain
again the food's improving okay so first
have stuff ready close food okay things
like that you need a job you need some
support second one by the way I'll take
a break in about five minutes okay I can
feel some peepee I have peepee
clairvoyance PP PP ESP okay number two
[Music]
it should not be a dangerous place okay
and this is especially 2,000 years ago
people would go out in the forest to do
meditation they would get robbed a lion
would eat them okay so the place should
be safe okay the place should be sick
and I have tried to do retreat in places
that were not really safe okay
it was not in you know they were like
weird people around or wild animals and
so should the place should be safe okay
comfortable and safe okay I told you
this story many times I tried to do a
retreat in a cave that came is not far
from Sedona it's a secret cave there's a
host 20 secret caves and they're in a
secret Canyon
nobody knows but it only takes about an
hour and to get there and I thought oh
I'm gonna be a real Miller if I you know
I will go to the secret came you know
and I found out secret caves have things
are living there already because if the
rain doesn't fall on you and the Sun
doesn't so in my cave there was a green
rattlesnake this is special Roslyn we
don't have it here but if they bite you
you die 100% you die so he was living
there and then there was a wolf
he was living there in the other corner
but the worst thing was about 2,000
spiders and these are not poisonous they
don't bite you they go they have these
long names today like so I suggest
number two write of the five of the six
a door I don't keep out the snake and
the wolf and okay don't be so romantic
about Himalaya cave it doesn't work okay
I really honestly it doesn't work there
are other people living there
alright number three the the generally
the the room you meditate in especially
in between shouldn't have like fungus or
swamps or things that make you sick
things that make you sing like the
shouldn't be wet the room is wet all the
time or too hot you know don't be a hero
when you pick a meditation spot pick a
nice one with a good temperature
not too hard not too cold okay the goal
is to meditate the goal is not to be a
tough guy okay no you have to choose
what you want if you want to be a tough
guy go in the cave I can show you where
it is you have to carry all your food it
takes about five hours you have to carry
all your food and you have choice have a
good meditation or have be a tough guy
nowadays I find a nice house in the
country owned by a rich person who's too
busy to go there and then I rent it from
them okay
and it's comfort of super comfortable
and I enjoy my and this other forest and
okay so many rich people build second
houses and never go there because
they're too busy there's many many
sedona has how many jb a couple of
hundred houses like that so don't ask
about two hundred houses like that the
people don't live there okay so good
place it's not gonna get you sick okay
not too wet I did a retreat in Ireland
forget that it rains all the time and
the place was cold and wet all the time
and we all got sick okay so don't don't
alright the third one fourth one you
it's very good if you can meditate if
you have friends who meditate meditation
friends okay it's like having yoga
friends I can do yoga every day from my
video
I have two favorite videos Bob Harper
and Maris Aylward I can do it every day
in my house I'm okay I can do yoga from
the video you know and I do but it's
more fun with my friends right Theresa
kicks you but it's more fun with your
friends okay so find meditation friends
especially if you do a retreat so get
five ten people and say I have a place
biggest one in the world it's my private
meditation in place let's go let's go
next let's go next spring make a plan
okay talk to talk to cinema okay and
it's cheap this is the cheapest place in
the world I think okay high quality all
right so have friends have good friends
the definition of a good friend in the
ancient meditation books is two things
number one that keep the ten good deeds
that's a good friend
that's a Dharma friend they they keep
the ten good is number one number two
they believe in emptiness okay maybe
they didn't see it yet but they believed
in it okay so better if you can find
meditation friends like that okay they
are not hurting other people they are
keeping their morality and they also are
hungry for Nagarjuna
number five and then we'll take a break
okay right during that day there should
not well two things during the day in
the night it should be a place where
there's not many other people where
there's not many other people okay the
ancient ancient books say a good
meditation place
I especially retreat no especially
retreat place should be about a mile and
a half away from anything okay and we
took a lot of trouble we looked for a
whole year to find this place we'd
looked for many many places and this one
is totally inconvenient nobody wants to
come run here the town is looks like a
nuclear bomb we've tried to find the
place where nobody's there
and in the world this is one of the
quietest places in the world it really
is one of the quietest places in the
room okay so there should not be many
people and it should be quiet okay no
highways near there
okay difficult to get there okay no city
nearby okay like that and we chose this
place because it's nowhere it took a
long time to find nowhere now you have
been to nowhere and come come on your
own don't wait for us to have a retreat
okay just come and have fun doing
machine is really fun the three
retreatants can tell you it's not easy
but you will never when you look back at
your long retreats you will say that's
the best thing I ever did in my life you
know that I really did something cool
right vimla I mean you look back at
those three years and you say that's the
best thing I ever did I think so it
wasn't easy but it's the best thing you
ever did right okay all right now the
best thing you can do is have a good pp
and we'll start in ten minutes
all right let's go back to this homework
[Music]
okay we only finished the first one
right five parts let's go to the second
one this typical getting micro class
Seder Chun chalk che do to choke shake
very very famous from the mother book of
Buddhism which is called by Stanley
bundle I'll be Dharma kosher okay very
famous meditation instruction dirt chung
choke hey okay du chun kosher okay and
it means like this okay be happy with
the things you own okay be happy with
the things you own I should show you my
shoes you won't get my shoes you know
which ones they're jig may know
something I'll sure I'll show you I'll
give a living example
okay these are beautiful shoes very old
okay they have a nice hole here so you
have to be careful when you go for a
walk at Diamond Mountain and but they're
so comfortable and you know Veronica
bought me two three pairs of new shoes
then when she's here I wear the new ones
she's coming this week Thursday okay but
when I'm alone I wear the old ones why
they're so soft and we are old friends
okay they know me I know pants also
today I did an operation on my pants
here cuz there's a big hole so I had to
cut it off so these are old friends of
mine
this is new shirt from Shenzhen I'm
sorry but these are old friends of mine
okay
Choki Choki RB dharma means make friends
with your old things and be happy be
satisfied Chak Chak means be satisfied
with what you have okay I'm happy about
my shoe it's comfortable it's soft it's
good for hiking the mountain very
strange
I can even wear it in a business suit if
I you know to you know be comfortable be
friends with your old things okay and
and think that's enough I'm happy
Chuck do Ching means don't go looking
for new friends okay
don't change your shoes every week okay
then you can't get to know them they
can't become old friend if you keep
buying new ones okay so this is very
powerful advice for meditators second
and third rules conditions of meditation
make friends with your old stuff your
old pants
shirt old shoes old house old husband
and make friends with your stuff and
don't don't go spending all your time in
the mall looking for new things okay
take be picky be careful what you buy
and buy something you really like and
then keep it for a long time and don't
be worrying about new things okay don't
be worrying about new things you will
always have extra money okay you will
not get into debt okay
it's more fun life is more fun when you
have extra money than if you have debt
okay then you can give money to the
students who give a good answer and you
have enough money if I have a lot of
possessions if I have an extra house if
I have extra car if I buy new shoes then
I won't have money to give to the
students you see so have extra money it
means be happy with what you have okay
be friends with your old stuff old
sweaters are really good okay they're
more soft so be careful what you buy be
picky what you buy and then buy
something that you can keep from and
then be satisfied okay and you will be a
better meditator you will be a better
meditator much better meditator okay
and you also have extra money and then
you can give your students money the
students like it okay so have extra
money don't spend on the money here
okay buy a few nice things and keep them
for a long time
get get become old friends I don't these
are how they are and they're really on
this whole I have to put some glue
and you'd be happier and you'll be a
better meditator okay don't go trying to
buy new things all the time
okay it will disturb your meditation
okay have a few old things in your house
they don't have to be ugly okay I didn't
say you have to be ugly they should be
cool and elegant and beautiful okay I
love your dress I told her three times
today I really like it and it's she said
gala it wasn't expensive I said but tell
everybody it was from Paris or something
okay
buy a few things that are beautiful and
elegant and soft and comfortable and
make friends with them and don't don't
be a bad friend to say I don't like you
anymore I'm gonna have a new friend
get to know your possessions and don't
change them all the time okay and your
meditation will be better I didn't say
don't be beautiful you should be
beautiful I didn't say you should wear
ugly clothes don't wear any clothes wear
soft old beautiful clothes okay
and sometimes buy something new and get
to know it okay but don't be these
people who there's a lady I know she had
to hire a guy to carry the bags from the
mall every day and she bought a big
house she goes home she throws them in
their closet she doesn't even open
doesn't take them out of the bag she has
a shopping addiction okay don't be like
that then you can't meditate your
meditation will be lousy okay
should you be beautiful yes should you
be handsome if you can can you have nice
clothes for sure just don't keep dumping
the ones and looking for new ones okay
you don't have time you your meditation
won't be good okay so now we got three
things you need a good place to meditate
you should be satisfied with your old
friends possessions and don't go you
know dumping your old friends for new
friends change friend every
that's not a very good friend okay those
are the first three okay two and three
are from where abhidharma where's number
one from my trail my tree okay sir
okay now number four right condition
number four don't be too busy don't be
too busy okay there's two kinds of busy
there's two kinds of busy John and
Connie are busy okay they have this
beautiful house in Sedona which is a
lonely house because they're never home
okay they're traveling to Singapore the
traveling to Mongolia travel to Taiwan
they're always traveling they're always
teaching okay they are busy so are they
breaking this number four no they are
busy with good things that's not busy
okay
busiest Netflix busiest text texting
people about the YouTube videos of cats
do not send me YouTube video cat video
when you call it links stop sending me
YouTube cat video links okay that's busy
okay
that's busy that's waste of time okay
busy means stupid things okay
busy means stupid things are you busy if
you're working at Diamond Mountain and
you never sleep no you're not busy
you're not busy you are creating the
cause for beautiful meditation okay your
meditation will be good okay shut karma
say shut karma shut you know karma karma
means to do shut means 100 and it means
a real meditator can do a hundred things
at once multitasking a real meditator
can multitask a hundred things at once
and they can do a good job and they can
still be happy and peaceful mind okay
so it doesn't mean you have to quit your
hospital mister move it's too big
yes the biggest one of the biggest
hospitals in China he's busy okay but
he's good busy okay he's not wasting his
time okay but okay but but but but but
but but but bingo people bingo bingo
just kidding it's again got it but never
break your practice never break your
practice okay no busy is worth your
practice okay do your yoga every day you
can take a day off every week you can
take two days off every week that might
even be better for your health okay and
you can take a day off from meditation
or two days off it's okay but five days
a week
practice okay taking a day off is a very
healthy thing that's a very good thing
that was a good idea I don't know who
invented it but it was a good idea okay
one or two days off a week that's fine
but there's no Dharma project
there's no good thing you can do
spiritual thing you can do that you
should break your meditation practice
and your yoga practice there is nothing
and your study okay there's nothing
which is that important okay nothing
okay Mahatma Gandhi who without violence
freedom one of the largest countries in
the world from the British right he's
supposed to meet the King of England
this is the most powerful person in the
world at that time it's like meeting Xi
Jinping or something okay so he has his
own appointment in the afternoon to meet
the king of England you know and then
his assistants said you know we gotta
make sure you're close all right you
know
and he said no I'm doing my meditation
and the guy said look III know your
spiritual guy it's okay but you are
meeting the King of England today you
don't have time to meditate and then
Gandhi Mahatma Gandhi said how much time
annotate usually one hour okay today two
hours then that's assistant is like what
we don't have time he says I want the
meeting to go well this is a very
important meeting 400 million people you
know I have to be ready I'm gonna double
my meditation today and he did and he
freed his country okay bye so when I say
busy can be a good thing helping other
people busy but if you break your
meditation practice or you break your
six times book practice or you break
your yoga practice or some other
physical exercise okay I don't care keep
going what's the other one tai chi
football I don't care
then then you broke then you you you
can't do that okay you will have a bad
life you will get sick you will die okay
okay then it then it doesn't matter if
you're busy because your body is gone
okay you need a body and you need a
healthy mind okay don't break your
practice for anybody or anything okay
don't break it okay don't break it for
anybody okay people say oh yeah say yeah
I'm sorry I practice I'm doing my
practice I'll see you at 11:00 I'll see
you at 10:00 the morning is mine people
try to get me to make phone calls to
change and stuff in the morning the
morning is mine okay I own the morning
okay I don't do other things okay all
right but don't be busy with stupid
things
what what wastin time is talking too
much to other people and movies and
things like that once a week once a
month go to a movie relax I've saw
Ostrom with Veronica it's a great movie
ok good for relaxing ok
but not every day ok not every day you
will waste your time ok how many we got
for ya number five keep your tank good
this tip keep your ten good deeds no
killing no stealing no sexual misconduct
no lying no slander no harsh words no
idle gossip no craving no ill-will no
wrong view keep your ten good deeds keep
you keep your book okay keep your book
what did some coppers say about
meditation
yeah the Karma to meditate is to keep
the ten good deeds
that's all it if you ask some copper
what do I need to meditate what kind of
cushion should I have shut up
should I put my right foot the first
time I left for the first shut up
is it okay if I am straight this way or
this way shut up
should I meditate in the morning or
evening shut up
what do you want me to do be nice to
other people then you can minute that's
the only cause of meditation okay you
don't need a diamond meditation me it
doesn't happen it doesn't matter what
cushion you have it doesn't matter how
you sit
nothing matters the best meditator in my
monastery he meditates lying down okay
if you have the Karma you can do it okay
what's the Karma be nice to other people
that's the ten good dates
okay what's the ten good deeds be nice
to other people don't hurt other people
that's all
and that's the cause of good meditation
that's the real cause of good meditation
DCI level 3 we teach them 29 different
things and at the end we tell them it
doesn't matter just be nice to other
people and your meditation will be sweet
okay and you can build a big meditation
retreat cabin and you can have 500
cushions imported from India with kusa
grass and you can have the blessing of
the big Lama on your finger and it won't
help you at all okay just be nice to
other people that's the real cause of
meditation okay
all right how many we got number six
don't waste your time with useless stuff
okay don't bother your head that guy the
guy I heard today I heard it today right
Jimmy who has cancer so I had problem
with some guy we had some disagreements
and now he has cancer he's gonna die in
two months or something then I'm
thinking like letting you know don't
waste your time worrying about other
people okay just stop it okay you don't
have time stop wasting your time okay I
don't like a shut up okay just don't
look at them or go away or do something
you know stop worrying about other
people okay you don't have time you
don't have time you know where are you
gonna go out to this you know we know
you're gonna die what day are you gonna
die that guy swear he died we're gonna
die and now he's gonna die you know you
don't have time to worry about useless
stuff okay and that's the biggest
obstacle to meditation the biggest
obstacle to meditation worry about
people who said something to you worry
so read the news the news is
to sell you more news okay it's not news
the news was written that the goal of
news is to make you worried so you will
read the news again tomorrow no really
they selling advertising they need you
to look at the news again tomorrow so if
they can worry you about something
they will try they will give you all the
bad news didn't you ever notice there's
no good news in the news it's like
what's it going on the world is a
dangerous place you have to read the
news tomorrow so are you gonna be in
trouble you know let it go don't read
the news okay I look at the news and
once a week for two minutes you know
then I know what's going on it's enough
okay you don't need to know everything
don't worry about don't worry about
other people don't worry about news okay
work on your practice you take care of
other people okay
don't waste your time you don't have
time okay you don't have time did I say
that you don't have time okay right JB
him and me were 26 yesterday now boom
were 60 what the 40 years ago
it just goes trust me when you get the
66 you can say Oh what happened don't
get you I was right you know don't waste
your time worrying about other people
forget just forget it okay someone hurts
you if you live forever I will say have
you try to hurt them if you're gonna
live forever you have time then try your
best to hurt them okay but you don't
have time so don't waste the time you
don't have time okay do sweet beautiful
things be with sweet beautiful people
whether your sweet beautiful old shoes
and don't waste your time when I was
stupid worrying about what somebody said
or somebody criticized you or just
forget it okay
you're gonna die they're gonna die okay
half the people who used to criticize me
are dead that's my approach I just I
just wait till they die you know I don't
worry I don't try to write a more better
internet defender she's my girl
I just went he died oh okay
that was finished all the problems you
have all the people who give you trouble
just wait them out
don't waste the time don't waste your
time in the time I didn't spend watching
movies and in the time I didn't spend
fighting with the people who want to
fight with me I translated more books
than anyone in the world okay because I
have time because I don't waste time on
people who give me problems I just
ignore them okay okay then you have more
time okay all right and your life is a
lot happier okay so you have someone
who's giving you trouble okay I went to
a teaching by the Dynamo okay many years
ago and I'll tell you this is a little
bit funny story okay there were 5,000
people it was at the Beacon Theatre in
New York so I went with this teeth with
the parents of one of my students their
parents invited me so I went and we're
sitting in this teacher this llama
somebody asks a question what should you
do if your neighbor always coming over
to your house and criticizing yelling
and he said well the first time they
come over just smile yeah then let them
yell okay they just smile
okay okay I understand I got it thank
you oh thank you so much you know I I
appreciate your concern you know then
the student asked what does they come a
second time
well the second time is even more
important you should smile be super nice
you know
they yelling at you some problem and you
know you know I understand you know okay
by the way the translator was from
Oxford University who taught Wow
so from Oxford University His Holiness
says that you on the second time you
should try to reason smile be reasonable
and then the students over what if they
come a same time then the mama said yeah
jump kappa so tell them kappa so then
i'm hope five thousand people are like
what's kept us on episode kappa zombies
tell them to eat then the oxford
guys tell them that you are very
uncomfortable
how's that when he's dead
come on you're not translating okay so
let it go let it go just let it go
have fun okay don't take life so
seriously okay don't don't be so serious
and don't listen to people who criticize
you just let it let it go okay
don't don't spend don't waste your time
even if your wife's in a bad mood right
just just you know let them talk finish
dinner and you know go have some ice
cream they're gonna get tired after a
while okay
don't fight with people don't waste your
time okay
yeah I can I already gave you that the
dates for Camila Sheila
7:58 de 750 ad that is for coming soon
you know the dates for my trailer - what
- 350 AD okay it's on your homework my
trailer okay and you know where the
teaching for all shoes come from old
comfortable shoes old friends and don't
go looking for new friends there's two
parts right du chun chokes a choke the
first one is the second the second one
is the first one choke chain means you
know be happy with your old friends and
then dirt chung means don't go looking
in the mall for three four more sets of
shoes okay be friends with the ones you
have okay got it
did i say you couldn't go shopping i
didn't say that i love shopping myself
did I say you can't look nice I didn't
say that I want you to look nice looking
nice as an offering to other people
Theresa Alpha is really cool and it's an
offering it's like a flower from your
heart right it's an offering to other
people that's a beautiful thing that's a
good thing I didn't say you can't
realize things I didn't say that you
should wear a nice thing it makes people
happy our job is supposed to be to make
other people happy if you look like a
homeless person then you're not gonna
make other people happy so try to look
nice other people for other people okay
it's like you're a flower you're
offering a flower okay all right